superclickz.com 2009-06-16

# superclickz.com

superclickz.com.com has the following Privacy Policy with respect to information gathered on its Web pages. 

The terms "we" and "us" refer to superclickz.com.com.

**The Information Collected**

This notice applies to all information collected on the superclickz.com.com Web site or submitted to superclickz.com.com at any time.  
Personally identifiable information then visiting superclickz.com.com and signing up for or using superclickz.com.com services, you may choose to supply superclickz.com.com with information that identifies you personally. This information may include the your name and contact information, as well as payment information. 

**The Way We Use Information**

We use the information you provide about yourself or others to complete the transaction for which the information is intended. Such transactions may include: administering a service, such as search, advertising sales, completing an order; replying to support requests; or contacting you if you have granted us permission to do so. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy we do not share this information with outside parties without your permission except to the extent that is necessary to administer the services or to comply in responding to legal proceedings.

We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways or for reasons unrelated to the ones described above without also providing an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**Data Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures reasonably designed to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Personnel who have access to our database are trained to maintain and secure all information.

**Access or Update Your Information**  
Members can access their information by logging in to their password-protected account and selecting "Edit Info."  
To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to your information.

**Contact**

Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please contact us.
